enomcentral.com 2016-12-26

# eNomCentral - domain name, web site hosting, email, registration

* * *

Last Updated: October 11, 2016

We know that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. **By visiting our website, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.** In this Privacy Policy, "we", "us" and "our" refer to eNom, Incorporated; eNom1039, Inc.; eNom1040, Inc.; eNom623, Inc.; eNom625, Inc.; Mobile Name Services Incorporated; Secure Business Services, Inc.; Sipence, Incorporated; Vedacore.com, Inc.; and Whois Privacy Protection Services, Inc.

#### What Personal Information About Customers Do We Gather?

  * **Information You Give Us:** We receive and store any information you enter on our website or give us in any other way. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, providing our services (e.g., domain name registration, DNS hosting, etc.), and communicating with you.
  * **Automatic Information:** We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many websites, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your browser accesses our sites. Examples of the information we collect and analyze include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; computer and connection information such as browser type and version, operating system, and platform; and the full Uniform Resource Locators (URL) click stream to, through, and from our website, including date and time. We use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track user movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.

#### What About Cookies?

  * Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser. Besides using the information as described above, we utilize cookies to control the flow of the ordering processes by maintaining the state of your online transactions.

Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) may use cookies on our website; however, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

#### Do We Share the Information We Receive?

Yes, we do share information we receive but only as described below. Otherwise we will not provide your personal information without your consent. We may be subject to liability in cases of onward transfer to third parties that do not conform with this Privacy Policy.

  * **WHOIS:** We are required by the Internet Corporation for Assigned Names and Numbers ("ICANN"), the organization that assumes responsibility for domain name allocation, to collect information about you during the domain name registration process. This information includes your full name, mailing address, phone number, email address, and, where provided, your facsimile number. ICANN then requires us to make your full name, mailing address, phone number, email address, and, where provided, your facsimile number, as well as the creation and expiration dates of your domain name registration and the name server information associated with your domain name ( "WHOIS Information"), available to the public via an interactive webpage and a "port 43" WHOIS service, unless you utilize a proxy service approved by us. In the event you elect to utilize a proxy service approved by us, the information of that proxy service, rather than your WHOIS Information, will be made available to the public. Please note that we are not able to control how members of the public may use the WHOIS Information.
  * **Affiliates.** We are a member of the Rightside Group, Ltd. family of companies (the "Family of Companies"). The Family of Companies includes the following U.S. based companies: Acquire This Name, Inc.; DomainSite, Inc.; eNom, Incorporated; eNom1039, Inc.; eNom1040, Inc.; eNom623, Inc.; eNom625, Inc.; Hot Media, Inc.; Mobile Name Services Incorporated; Name.com, Inc.; Name.net, Inc.; Name104, Inc.; Name105, Inc.; Name106, Inc.; Name107, Inc.; Name108, Inc.; Name109, Inc.; Name110, Inc.; Name111, Inc.; Name112, Inc.; Name113, Inc.; Name114, Inc.; Name115, Inc.; Name116, Inc.; Name117, Inc.; Name118, Inc.; Name119, Inc.; Name120, Inc.; Rightside Group, Ltd.; Rightside Operating Co.; Secure Business Services, Inc.; Sipence, Incorporated; Vedacore.com, Inc.; and Whois Privacy Protection Services, Inc. The Family of Companies also includes the following non-U.S. based companies: Bejing United TLD Tech Co., Ltd.; DMIH Limited; eNom Canada Corp.; Rightside Australia Pty Ltd; Rightside Canada, Inc.; Rightside Domains Europe Limited; and United TLD Holdco Ltd. We may share information we have about you within the Family of Companies to facilitate, support, and integrate their activities and improve our services. Each U.S. based member of the Family of Companies adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles (as discussed below). 
  * **Advertisers:** We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. 
  * **Partners:** We partner with other parties to provide specific services. When the user signs up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. 
  * **Agents:** We engage other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include processing credit card payments, providing marketing assistance, providing customer services, sending postal mail and email to you, removing repetitive information from customer lists, and analyzing data. These persons have access to personal information needed to perform their functions. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information that you provide to us for any secondary purposes. 
  * **Service Providers:** We engage other companies and individuals to perform enhanced services on our behalf. In addition, certain of our enhanced services require that we contact Internet directories and various search engines on your behalf. Many of our service providers have access to personal information needed to perform their services. These parties are not allowed to use personally identifiable information except for the purpose of providing these services. 
  * **Business Transfer:** As we continue to develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or their assets. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. Also, if we or all or substantially all of our assets were ever to be acquired, customer information will of course be one of the transferred assets.
  * **Compliance:** We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate in response to a lawful request by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements; enforce or apply our agreements; or protect our rights, property, or safety, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

#### How Secure Is Information About Me?

  * We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input and the information we may send to our agents.
  * We have gone to great lengths to ensure your information is securely obtained and held in compliance with the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard. For example, we encrypt your credit card number before it is stored in our database. This helps ensure that no one may access your credit card from our system.
  * It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer.

#### What Information Can I Access?

  * We give you access to certain information about you for the limited purpose of viewing and, in certain cases, updating that information. To view or change this information, log in to your account. When you update information, we usually keep a copy of the prior version for our records.

#### Links

  * Sites provided by us contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website.

#### Children

  * We do not sell services for purchase by children. If you are under 18, you may use our services only with involvement of a parent or guardian.

#### Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions 

  * If you choose to visit our website, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our terms and conditions, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of Washington. If you have any concern about our privacy practices, please send us a thorough description to [legalnotice@rightside.co](mailto:legalnotice@rightside.co), and we will try to resolve it. Our business changes constantly. This Privacy Policy and our terms and conditions will change also, and use of information that we gather now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of use. We may email reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our website frequently to see recent changes.

#### For European Union Citizens or Switzerland Citizens

_EU-US Privacy Shield Framework_

  * We comply with the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries. We have certified that we adhere to the Privacy Shield Principles of Notice, Choice, Accountability for Onward Transfer, Security, Data Integrity and Purpose Limitation, Access, and Recourse, Enforcement and Liability. If there is any conflict between the policies in this Privacy Policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification page, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/>
  * Note that you have the right to access, correct, or delete your personal data processed by us. Some personal data can be accessed, corrected, and deleted through your account. For assistance with accessing, correcting, or deleting your personal data, please contact us at [legalnotice@rightside.co](mailto:legalnotice@rightside.co). Please be aware that deleting your personal data may result in termination of the services you receive through us.
  * In compliance with the EU-US Privacy Shield Principles, we commit to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. European Union individuals with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact our parent company, Rightside Group, Ltd., at [legalnotice@rightside.co](mailto:legalnotice@rightside.co), or by postal mail at: Rightside Group, Ltd., Attn: Legal Department, 5808 Lake Washington Blvd NE, Suite 300, Kirkland, WA 98033 USA
  * We have further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the EU-US Privacy Shield Principles BBB EU PRIVACY SHIELD, a non-profit alternative dispute resolution provider located in the United States and operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, please visit www.bbb.org/EU-privacy-shield/for-eu-consumers/ for more information and to file a complaint. In addition, it is possible, under certain limited conditions, for individuals to invoke binding arbitration before the Privacy Shield Panel to be created by the US Department of Commerce and the European Commission. Note that the US Federal Trade Commission (FTC) has enforcement authority over our compliance with this Privacy Policy.

_US-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework_

  * We comply with the US-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from Switzerland. We have certified that we adhere to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, accountability for onward transfer, security, data integrity and purpose limitation, access, and recourse, enforcement and liability. If there is any conflict between the policies in this Privacy Policy and the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles, the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles shall govern. To learn more about the US-Swiss Safe Harbor and to view our certification page, please visit <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/>
  * In compliance with the US-Swiss Safe Harbor Principles, we commit to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information. Swiss citizens with inquiries or complaints regarding this privacy policy should first contact our parent company, Rightside Group, Ltd., at [legalnotice@rightside.co](mailto:legalnotice@rightside.co), or by postal mail at: Rightside Group, Ltd., Attn: Legal Department, 5808 Lake Washington Blvd NE, Suite 300, Kirkland, WA 98033 USA.
  * We have further committed to refer unresolved privacy complaints under the US-Swiss Safe Harbor to an independent dispute resolution mechanism operated by the Council of Better Business Bureaus. If you do not receive timely acknowledgment of your complaint, or if your complaint is not satisfactorily addressed, please visit www.bbb.org/us/safe-harbor-complaints for more information and to file a complaint.
